Hello friends, welcome to all of you
in information and general and friends, we are going to
talk about ice cream in the big of the Sir family, the
people in the Sir family who had deposited money for
their earnings, their money was stuck,
after a long wait, a
good news that Amit Shah has
started the Sahara refund portal on Tuesday, so let
us know how we can withdraw our deposited money in Sahara,
so let us know step by step
what is the process, what all will have to be done,
before starting the video, I request all of you
fans to subscribe to our channel and also
press the bell icon so that you keep getting
notifications of whatever we post, while starting the video, let us
also tell you friends, we will
know about the Sahara India refund portal,
Sir, for the first time in India, more than 10 crore
investors have got relief, now
their money will be returned soon, for this the
government has launched the Sahara India refund portal, with the
release of this portal, now
those people
whose money is stuck in Sahara will be able to get their money back online, with the release of the portal,
Sahara's tax cooperative society
Applicants will be able to apply. Let us know
what is the process in detail. Let
us know what
is the process for refund. Process number one, for this, first of all
investors will have to
login on the website of MORCAFUND.crcs.gov.in,
after that on the home page of the portal,
click on Submit Registration.
Friends, I am telling you that the second option is to
click on Submit Registration on the home page of the portal, after that a
page like this will open and here you will have to
enter the last 4 digits of the Aadhaar number and the
mobile number in Aadhaar will have to be entered here.
If we talk about the third option, then here
you will have to enter your Aadhaar number and the
mobile number linked to it, which we have already
told, after that on the fourth number,
after this you will
click on Send OTP and enter the OTP, that is,
when you click on Send OTP,
an OTP will come on your mobile, you will have to
enter it here. After the registration is
completed, click on Submit Login, so
this is the fifth option.
If we talk about registration, then after this again you will have to enter the
last 4 digits of Aadhaar number and mobile number and
enter the OTP
in the seventh option.  After reading the terms and conditions,
click on "I agree." Here, your
bank name and date of birth will appear
in the eighth option. After this, you will have to
fill the claim request form along with the depositor certificate and the
name of the society, membership number and deposit amount.
After all these processes,
in the ninth option, after entering and verifying all the details,
you will have to download the claim letter on the portal,
paste your passport size photo on it and
sign it.
In the tenth option, after this,
you should again load the claim letter. As soon as it is
successful, a confirmation message will be sent to your registered mobile number.
If we talk about the 11th option, after this, the
claim amount will be transferred to your Aadhaar linked
account within 45 days. So
friends, in this video, I told you how
you will be
able to withdraw your deposited money from the Sahara Refund Portal. So, this is the
process. After completing this process, you will have to
wait for 45 days and as it is being
said that within 45 days,
your money will be deposited in your account. So,
we hope that this is the process.
You all must have liked this video, let
us take a look and talk about which applicants
can apply. Those who had invested in the Sahara Co-operative
Society's tax
societies can
apply for refund of their money on this portal. Around 2.5 crore people have deposited up to Rs 30,000 in 4 cooperative
societies - Sahara Credit Cooperative Society
Limited, Sahara N Universal Multipurpose
Society Limited, Hamara India Credit
Cooperative Society Limited and Tara
Multipurpose Cooperative Society Limited
and those who are in the same tax
cooperative society
can apply, so
like, share and yes
subscribe to the channel and also click on the bell icon
so that you keep getting updates of new videos.
Thank you.